Things were busy that summer.
The frequent disasters of the
past year probably played a role,
but cursed spirits were
springing up like maggots.
Exorcise, absorb.
Over and over.
Exorcise.
Absorb.
No one else understands
what cursed spirits taste like.
It's like swallowing a dirty rag that's
been used to clean up shit and vomit.
Exorcise.
Absorb.
"What I witnessed isn't uncommon."
"I understood the ugliness of the masses,
and still chose to be a
jujutsu sorcerer who saves others."
That's what I've been telling
myself ever since that day.
Ever since that day.
Apparently, this used to be
the home of the president
of a company managing a local
chain of barbecue restaurants.
However, in July of last year,
the mad cow disease breakout dealt
a fatal blow to his restaurants,
so he committed suicide with his family
after they were buried under vast debt.
From then on, local rumors claimed
the president's home was haunted,
so local school kids, college students
from outside the prefecture,
job-hoppers, and others would visit
it as part of a test of courage,
and subsequently go missing.
Those rumors brought about more rumors,
and the damage just continued to spread.
Rumors do tend to spread rather
quickly around haunted spots.
They can spread at an unbelievable
pace nowadays, thanks to the Internet.
This all just means even more
work for us jujutsu sorcerers.
In addition to that, three grade school kids
went missing on their way home from school.
There's also a high chance
the families, police, colleagues,
and friends who trace the paths
of those who disappeared
will reach the mansion and
become victims themselves.
We have to sever the root of
this issue as soon as possible.
HQ sent us to investigate because
they reached the same conclusion.
Warning!
Entering These Premises Is Forbidden!
Many Have Gone Missing!
They're even paying my fees,
which aren't cheap.
Did you overcharge them again?
You make it sound so bad.
Call it negotiation.
We're here.
Let's go, then.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Emerge from darkness, blacker than darkness.
Purify that—
There's no need for a veil.
Huh?
I don't sense the presence of any Curses.
The cause is almost certainly
inside the building.
You can cast the veil later if we
end up attacking it from outside.
...True.
It's unlocked.
Seems like something's blocking the door.
What is all this?
Mei-san.
It's here.
And it's all around us, too.
Let's get going.
I don't need that, but you do, right?
Thank you.
All right.
I-Incredible.
Oh, it still has electricity.
For now, let's have a
look inside the building.
I'll take this floor,
you take the second.
Huh? All by myself?
Is there a problem with that?
N-No, i-it's fine.
Off you go, then.
Okay.
This is the last one.
You could be the next big Scream Queen.
Jeez!
Please don't startle me like that!
You got startled all on your own.
Are you done exploring the first floor?
This is the first floor.
Huh?
I was walking down
the first floor hallway.
What? But...
I know I entered a room
at the end of the hallway...
A box of candy.
A bag of potato chips.
Cans.
A backpack.
A sweatshirt.
I've already seen this three times.
And see these marks? I made
them on my way through here.
It would seem that we're already
in the belly of the beast.
Huh?
For real?
How long is this hallway?
We've been moving for thirty minutes,
so about four kilometers so far.
It's not an innate domain, is it?
It's not.
Those are manifestations
of the spirit's mindscape.
Which means...
This is a barrier.
Correct.
Most likely, the victims
were trapped inside this
and then killed by the cursed spirit.
Though, considering the
use of this technique,
the cursed spirit itself should be weak.
So if we can just escape this barrier...
Now, quiz time.
How would you break this, Utahime?
This hallway is repeating itself.
At first...
I thought...
I'm surprised you could touch them.
...it was shaped like a donut.
But we passed by four of
the marks you made, right?
When I calculated how many
paces apart they were, I got...
122,
203,
157,
and 270 paces.
So the spacing between marks was random.
I see.
The interval between
repetitions isn't standardized.
Which means that, most likely...
this barrier is patching spaces together.
So if we both run down the hallway
at top speed, then at some point...
It'll break.
Close. Ninety points.
D'oh.
What's the remaining ten?
When we run, we do so in opposite
directions at the same time.
I get it!
So my patching theory was correct,
and if we quickly advance
in different directions,
that makes it harder for the cursed
spirit to hold the barrier together.
And once we have that opening,
we might be able to get out.
One hundred points.
Then, with that settled...
If this works, I'll be expecting a promotion.
How much do you have in savings?
What?
Never mind. I'll think about it.
Right!
Okay... Ready, set...
Go!
We did it!
Wait, wha—
I'm here to save you,
Utahime.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Hidden Inventory/Premature Death
m 0 0 l 140 0 l 140 200 l 0 200
Jujutsu High
Second-Year
Gojo
Satoru
Are you crying?
I'm not crying!
m 0 0 l 100 0 l 100 140 l 0 140
Second-grade
Sorcerer
Iori
Utahime
And be more polite!
If I was crying, would you console me?
m 0 0 l 140 0 l 140 200 l 0 200
First-grade
Sorcerer
Mei Mei
I'd certainly appreciate that.
Nah, you wouldn't cry, Mei-san.
You're strong.
That so?
Gojo! You listen here!
I don't need your hel—
Don't swallow it.
I'll absorb it later.
Satoru, it's not nice to pick on the weak.
m 0 0 l 136 0 l 136 200 l 0 200
Jujutsu High
Second-Year
Geto
Suguru
What kind of idiot picks on the strong?
You're the one fanning the flames
like it comes naturally, Geto-kun.
Utahime-senpai!
Are you okay?
Shoko!
m 0 0 l 136 0 l 136 200 l 0 200
Jujutsu High
Second-Year
Ieiri
Shoko
I was worried about you.
We hadn't heard from you for two whole days.
Shoko!
Shoko! Don't let yourself
turn out like those two!
I won't turn into trash like them.
m 0 0 l 50 0 l 50 140 l 0 140
Said
Trash
The path Utahime walked is falling apart.
Shut up.
Wait, two days?
Ah, was the cursed spirit's barrier
one of those that messes with time?
They're rare, but they
do happen now and then.
I thought it was odd,
since Mei-san was with you.
Seems like it was.
Something the matter?
No. Just realized that means
it was actually two days' labor,
and that means extra fees paid out to me.
She's planning to overcharge again.
That aside, what about the veil, you three?
White
\h\hNews
Degradation of gas pipes causes explosion
Next, the explosion that occurred
yesterday in Hamamatsu, Shizuoka.
One of you three said they
would cast the veil themselves
The explosion was caused
by degradation of gas pipes.
Our reporter on the scene...
and left your assistant
supervisor behind, didn't you?
And then you forgot the veil.
m 0 0 l 126 0 l 126 184 l 0 184
First-grade
Sorcerer
Yaga
Masamichi
Come forward.
Sensei!
Why don't we stop this hunt for the culprit?!
So it was you, Satoru.
Discipline
Is a veil that necessary in the first place?
It's not like it matters if
normies see or not, right?
They can't see cursed spirits
or cursed techniques, anyway.
Of course it's not good for them to see.
The strongest deterrent
against the outbreak
of a cursed spirit is the
mental calm of the populace.
That's exactly why we have to conceal
the threats they can't even
see as much as possible.
And that's not all—
Yeah, yeah, I get it.
Looking out for the weak
is so exhausting, honestly.
Survival of the weakest.
That's how a society should be.
The weak help each other and
discourage any who are too strong.
Listen, Satoru.
Jujutsu exists to protect
non-jujutsu sorcerers.
Is that your moral argument?
I hate moral arguments.
What?
Assigning reasons and
responsibility to strength
is what those who are weak do.
Quit making yourself feel
better by spouting bullshit.
Blegh.
Run for it.
Want to take this outside, Satoru?
You feeling lonely?
Go by yourself.
How long are you going
to keep fooling around?
Where did Shoko go?
Who knows?
Bathroom, probably.
Whatever.
This mission is being assigned to you two.
What are those faces for?
Nothing.
Frankly, I think it's too much for you,
but Tengen-sama asked for you specifically.
Your mission has two goals.
The Star Plasma Vessel
is the one compatible with Tengen-sama.
You are to escort that girl and erase her.
Escort a brat and erase her?
That's right.
Have you finally gone senile?
It is spring.
He's probably got his head full
with being the next principal.
Jokes aside, though—
I'll be the one to decide
if I let that off as a joke.
Is this about renewing
Tengen-sama's technique?
What's that?
What?
Tengen-sama possesses the
cursed technique of Immortality,
but it is not Eternal Youth.
It wouldn't be an issue
if all he did was get older,
but after his body ages to a certain point,
the cursed technique
begins rewriting his body.
Evolution.
He'll cease to be human and become
a higher form of existence.
What's wrong with that?
Sounds cool.
According to Tengen-sama,
those who reach that state
of being have no will.
It means Tengen-sama would
cease to be Tengen-sama.
Tokyo Jujutsu High School
All the jujutsu schools,
the barriers that form the
foundation of jujutsu society,
the many barrier techniques
of the assistant supervisors...
They're all being strengthened by Tengen-sama.
Without the aid of his power,
we could hardly maintain security
or clean up after missions.
In the worst-case scenario,
Tengen-sama could even become
a threat to mankind.
That's why, every 500 years,
he finds the Plasma Star Vessel—
someone who is compatible with him—
and assimilates them,
overwriting the information of their body.
By renewing his body,
he resets his cursed
technique back to the start
and avoids Evolution.
I get it.
It would be fine if he turned
into MetalGreymon,
but we can't have him
becoming SkullGreymon.
So we have him start over from Koromon.
What? Yeah, sure, that works.
The Star Plasma Vessel's
location has been leaked.
Right now, there are two major
groups after the young girl's life.
One is the Curse User Group Q,
which seeks to upend jujutsu society
with Tengen-sama's rampage.
The other is the Star Religious
Group, also known as the
"Time Vessel Association,"
which worships Tengen-sama as a god.
Tengen-sama will assimilate the
Star Plasma Vessel two days from now.
You are to protect the girl until then and
ensure that she reaches Tengen-sama!
If you fail, the effects will ripple
throughout even normal society!
Don't forget that!
Yeah, but you know,
I get why Curse User Group Q
would be after her,
but why would this Star Religious
Group want to kill a brat?
Their object of worship is
the pure form of Tengen-sama.
Allowing the Star Plasma Vessel—
in their minds, an impurity—
to blend into him is unforgivable.
The Star Religious Group is an
organization of non-sorcerers.
I don't think we need to pay them any mind.
The ones to be wary of are Q.
Well, I'm sure it'll be fine.
We're the strongest, after all.
That's why Tengen-sama asked
for us specifically, right?
What is it?
You know, Satoru...
I've been wanting to say this for a while,
but you should stop being
so full of yourself.
Huh?!
Especially when you're
addressing your superiors.
We might end up meeting
Tengen-sama, after all.
You should be more polite and humble.
You'd scare your juniors less, too.
Hah!
Screw that!
Come on, Satoru.
Whatever.
I'll bring it up again later.
Coming.
Huh?
You alive?
I am, at least.
You think we'll be blamed
if the brat died from that?
Ah
Don't blame me.
If you must hate someone, hate Tengen.
m 0 0 l 112 0 l 112 164 l 0 164
Q
Combatant
Kokun
Wha—
Would you please stop making us stand out?
We just got chewed out
for that this morning.
So this girl is the Star Plasma Vessel?
I know those uniforms. You're
sorcerers from Jujutsu High, right?
Hand over the kid.
Or I'll kill you.
Can't hear you.
Come closer and talk.
Man, barely safe.
Wonderful.
You're Gojo Satoru, right?
m 0 0 l 136 0 l 136 164 l 0 164
Q
Combatant
Bayer
You're famous.
I hear you're strong.
Let me find out if the rumors are true.
I'm down for that, but let's set some rules.
Rules?
I don't want to get yelled
at for going overboard.
So if you cry and apologize,
I won't kill you.
That's our rule.
Damn brat.
It's started.
The Star Religious Group doesn't have the
power to fight against jujutsu sorcerers.
But they can pay very well.
That I guarantee.
How about it, Zen'in?
Want to get in on the assassination
of the Star Plasma Vessel?
I'm not a Zen'in anymore.
I took my wife's name.
It's Fushiguro now.
But sure.
Count me in.
Episode 25
Hidden Inventory
You know how there are some
words you can't get out of
your head, even though they
have no connection to you?
Like "The Privatization of
Reclaimed Lands in Perpetuity Act"?
Yeah! Or like "Corporate Governance."
Please look forward to the next
episode, "Hidden Inventory 2"!
Next Episode
Hidden Inventory 2
You tell us one, too, Shoko.
Chagu Chagu Umakko.